Diane Wolkstein collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Story Performances
  - Subseries 3: Audio and Video
    - The Day Ocean Came to Visit, September 30, 2001, AFC 2016/057: SR109; 1 sound cassette
    - Deena Metzer, Michael, Diane, 1988, AFC 2016/057: SR110; 1 sound cassette
    - Devils, Dances, and Whiskers: Folk Tales from Haiti, 1993, afc2016057_dc119; 8 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - The Diamond, October 20, 2003, afc2016057_dc439; Performed at Cedar Crest Village; 8 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Diane Wolkstein, October 29, 2001, AFC 2016/057: SR111; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Diane Wolkstein and Ben Haggarty, June 3, 2000, AFC 2016/057: SR112; 1 sound cassette
    - Diane Wolkstein and Billy Edd Wheeler, April 27, 1972, AFC 2016/057: SR113; 1 sound tape reel: 10 in.
    - Diane Wolkstein and Jeff Greene, January 2, 2010, AFC 2016/057: SR114; 1 sound cassette
    - Diane Wolkstein and Joan Bodger, June 19, 1999, AFC 2016/057: SR115; 1 sound cassette
    - Diane Wolkstein and Shirley Keller planning, September 15, 2012, AFC 2016/057: SR116; 1 sound cassette
    - Diane Wolkstein with Renata Rosa, July 1, 2000, AFC 2016/057: SR117; 1 sound cassette
    - Diana and Therese, June 17, 2005, AFC 2016/057: MV076; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Diane Tells Fairy Tales from Estonia, April 29, 1994, AFC 2016/057: MV077; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Dodge Poetry Festival, Diane Wolkstein storytelling, 8:00-8:45am, September 29, 2006, afc2016057_dc015; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Dodge Poetry Festival, Diane Wolkstein storytelling, 12:00-12:30pm, September 29, 2006, afc2016057_dc012; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Dodge Poetry Festival,Diane Wolkstein storytelling, 12:00-1:00pm, September 30, 2006
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc013; 8 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc014; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Dodge Poetry Festival, Diane Wolkstein storytelling, 8:00-9:15am, October 1, 2006, afc2016057_dc011; 8 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Dodge Poetry Festival, Diane Wolkstein storytelling, 2006, afc2016057_dc029; 1 video file (MOV)
    - Side A: Doll's Day for Yoshiko, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR118; 1 sound cassette
    - Dream Songs, January 2, 1993, AFC 2016/057: SR119; 1 sound cassette
    - Dream Songs, March 1993, AFC 2016/057: SR120; 1 sound cassette
    - Dream Songs, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR121; 1 sound cassette
    - Dream Songs rehearsal, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR122; 1 sound cassette
    - Drunkards and Watercarriers, March 6, 1989, Diane Wolkstein with Shlomo Carlebach at the American Museum of Natural History
      - Part 1, afc2016057_dc105; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Part 2, afc2016057_dc106; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Eliahu and Miriam, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR123; 1 sound cassette
    - Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep, September 28, 1985, AFC 2016/057: SR124; 1 sound cassette
    - Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep, September 21, 1991
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV085; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV086; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV087; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep, September 16, 1995, AFC 2016/057: MV088; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep, September 21, 1996, AFC 2016/057: MV091; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep, September 22, 1996, AFC 2016/057: MV089; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep, September 20, 1997
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV090; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc022; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep, September 15, 2007
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV084; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc473; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep, September 15, 2012, afc2016057_dc424; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR125; 1 sound cassette
    - Elsie Piddock, Ugly Duckling, September 21, 1991, AFC 2016/057: MV092; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - English Folk Tales, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR126; 1 sound cassette
    - Epic of Gilgamesh, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR127; 1 sound cassette
    - Eskimo Stories and Poems, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR128; 1 sound cassette
    - Eskimo Stories and Poems, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR129; 1 sound cassette
    - Eskimo Stories and Songs, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR130; 1 sound cassette
    - Eskimo Stories; Breath of Life, February 15, 1990, AFC 2016/057: SR131; 1 sound cassette
    - Eskimo Tales, February 15, 1990, AFC 2016/057: SR132; 1 sound cassette
    - Eskimo Tales, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR133; 1 sound cassette
    - Esther's Story, March 3, 1984
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV096; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV097; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Esther's Story, March 8, 1989, AFC 2016/057: SR134; 1 sound cassette
    - Esther's Story, April 18, 1991, AFC 2016/057: SR135; 1 sound cassette
    - Esther's Story, February 17, 1996, AFC 2016/057: MV093; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Esther's Story, 1996
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV098; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc026; Edited copy made from MiniDV; Shirley Keller; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Esther's Story on The Folk People Show, 1996
      - Part 1, AFC 2016/057: MV330; 1 videocassette (DVCam)
      - Part 2, AFC 2016/057: MV331; 1 videocassette (DVCam)
      - Parts 1 and 2, AFC 2016/057: MV333; 1 videocassette (BetacamSP)
    - Esther's Story, 1999, AFC 2016/057: MV095; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Esther's Story, undated
      - Pictures, AFC 2016/057: MV094; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Parts 1 and 2, AFC 2016/057: MV099; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR136; 1 sound cassette
    - Exodus, April 10, 1999, AFC 2016/057: SR137; 1 sound cassette
    - Exodus, April 11, 1999
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV100; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV101; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 1A - MiniDV, AFC 2016/057: MV103; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 1B - MiniDV, AFC 2016/057: MV104; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2A - MiniDV, AFC 2016/057: MV105; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2B - MiniDV, AFC 2016/057: MV106; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 3A - MiniDV, AFC 2016/057: MV107; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 3B - MiniDV, AFC 2016/057: MV108; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 1 - MiniDV, AFC 2016/057: MV109; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2 - MiniDV, AFC 2016/057: MV110; Lunch, music, dancing; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 3 - MiniDV, AFC 2016/057: MV111; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc274; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR138; 1 sound cassette
    - Exodus - Marley sampler, 1999, AFC 2016/057: SR204; 1 sound cassette
    - Exodus, 1999, Part 7 (SR147) and Part 8 (SR148) were deaccessioned, as both tapes were blank.
      - Part 1, AFC 2016/057: SR141; 1 sound cassette
      - Part 2, AFC 2016/057: SR142; 1 sound cassette
      - Part 3, AFC 2016/057: SR143; 1 sound cassette
      - Part 4, AFC 2016/057: SR144; 1 sound cassette
      - Part 5, AFC 2016/057: SR145; 1 sound cassette
      - Part 6, AFC 2016/057: SR146; 1 sound cassette
    - Exodus, April 3, 2000, AFC 2016/057: SR139; 1 sound cassette
    - Exodus, July 3, 2000, AFC 2016/057: SR140; 1 sound cassette
    - Exodus, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV102; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Family Program Seattle, Washington, February 24, 1985, AFC 2016/057: SR149; 1 sound cassette
    - Fattest of All and other stories, June 10, 2000, AFC 2016/057: SR150; 1 sound cassette
    - Fiddler of High Lonesome, undated
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR151; 1 sound cassette
      - Sound reel version, AFC 2016/057: SR255; 1 sound tape reel: 5 in.
      - CD version, afc2016057_dc307; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - Gala of Cat, February 1993, AFC 2016/057: SR152; 1 sound cassette
    - The Gizzard and other stories, July 3, 1999, AFC 2016/057: SR153; 1 sound cassette
    - Glass Mountain; Bouki Dances, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV112; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Glass Mountain, May 2, 1999, AFC 2016/057: SR154; 1 sound cassette
    - The Grass Slipper; The Nightingale, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR155; 1 sound cassette
    - Side A: Grimm Folk Tales; Side B: African Folk Tales, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR156; 1 sound cassette
    - Gumpy - pirate, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR157; 1 sound cassette
    - Haitian Songs and Stories, 1993, AFC 2016/057: MV308; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Haitian Songs and Stories, June 10, 1995
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV114; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc021; Performed at the Hans Christian Andersen statue. Music by Shirley Keller.; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Haitian Songs and Stories, June 26, 1999
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV113; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc027; Camera I. Performed at the Hans Christian Andersen statue. Music by Shirley Keller.; Steven C. Keller; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc028; Camera II. Performed at the Hans Christian Andersen statue. Music by Shirley Keller.; Phillip David; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Haitian Songs and Stories, May 9, 2010, afc2016057_dc114; Performance with Joy Kelly of Horse and Toad and One, My Darling, Come to Mama at A Benefit for Haiti: The Stories; 11 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Hatienne tape with Diane Wolkstein, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR159; 1 sound tape reel: 10 in.
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, September 29, 1973, AFC 2016/057: MV309; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, April 1, 1981, AFC 2016/057: SR158; 1 sound tape reel: 10 in.
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, May 29, 1990, AFC 2016/057: SR244; 1 sound cassette
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, September 1991, afc2016057_dc416; Ugly Duckling, Pig Wisps, and Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep. Music by Shirley Keller.; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, June 17, 1995
      - Hi8 version, AFC 2016/057: MV318; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc446; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, Trudy Betcher, July 10, 1995, AFC 2016/057: MV339; 1 film reel (16mm)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, September 20, 1997, afc2016057_dc417; Kokioko, Ugly Duckling, and Elsie Piddock; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, June 26, 1999, AFC 2016/057: MV316; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, October 2, 2002, afc2016057_dc058; 6 sound files (WAV)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, January 6, 2005, afc2016057_dc039; Stories include: Hans Clodhopper, The Goblin and the Grocer, The Ugly Duckling, The Emperor's New Clothes, The Nightingale, and Dance, Dance, Dolly Mine; The Works, Inc. for August House; 6 sound files (WAV)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, April 2, 2005
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV198; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV197; 200th birthday celebration for Hans Christian Andersen; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, September 17, 2005, afc2016057_dc112; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, Elsie Piddock and Squirrel, September 16, 2006, AFC 2016/057: MV196; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, 2006, AFC 2016/057: MV115; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, June 7, 2007, AFC 2016/057: MV072; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, June 30, 2007
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV116; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV117; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, September 15, 2007
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc016; Accompanied by Shirley Keller and Bruce Markow; Charles Pruett; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc017; Accompanied by Shirley Keller and Bruce Markow; Charles Pruett; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, September 12, 2009, afc2016057_dc445; Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep. Guests: Rikki Borge, Rolf Stang portraying Hans Christian Andersen, Shirley Keller, and Len Rambusch; 8 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, September 15, 2012, afc2016057_dc025; Accompanied by Shirley Keller; Moses Gorgas; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Hans Christian Andersen statue, Stories told in Central Park, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV319; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Her Dance, June 22, 2007, afc2016057_dc018; Shirley Keller; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Hurricane Katrina Benefit performance, November 10, 2007, Performance at Scandinavian House. Contains performances by other performers as well as a storytelling performance by Diane Wolkstein; Shirley Keller
      - Part 1, afc2016057_dc051; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Part 2, afc2016057_dc095; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Hurry Hurry Time - Master, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR160; 1 sound cassette
    - I Can't Love You Anymore, Nightingale, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR161; 1 sound cassette
    - In the Spirit, April 1, 2004, AFC 2016/057: SR162; 1 sound cassette
    - Inanna Ballet, undated, afc2016057_dc253; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Inanna Ballet and Descent of Inanna, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV204; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Inanna Opera, November 6, 2005, Performed at Dominican University of California; Marcia Burchard
      - Introductory remarks by Diane Wolkstein, afc2016057_dc464; 1 sound file (WAV)
      - Opera, afc2016057_dc465; 14 sound files (WAV)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, September 10, 1983, AFC 2016/057: SR166; 1 sound cassette
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, June 7, 1984
      - VHS version, AFC 2016/057: MV211; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - VHS version, AFC 2016/057: MV218; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - VHS version, AFC 2016/057: MV219; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR165; 1 sound cassette
      - Part 1 - sound reel, AFC 2016/057: SR169; 1 sound tape reel: 7 in.
      - Part 2 - sound reel, AFC 2016/057: SR170; 1 sound tape reel: 7 in.
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, April 28, 2000
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR163; Rehearsal; 1 sound cassette
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR168; 1 sound cassette
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, March 26, 2001, AFC 2016/057: MV200; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, 2001
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV075; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - VHS version, AFC 2016/057: MV214; Master #2; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, September 29, 2006, AFC 2016/057: MV202; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, March 15, 2007, afc2016057_dc031; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, March 28, 2007, afc2016057_dc032; Version 3; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, April 7, 2009, afc2016057_dc477; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, April 17, 2009, afc2016057_dc478; 2 sound files (WAV)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV201; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated
      - Performance 1, AFC 2016/057: MV205; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Performance 2, AFC 2016/057: MV209; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Performance 3, AFC 2016/057: MV210; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated
      - Rehearsal 1, AFC 2016/057: MV215; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Rehearsal 2, AFC 2016/057: MV216; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated
      - Part 1, AFC 2016/057: SR171; 1 sound tape reel: 7 in.
      - Part 2, AFC 2016/057: SR172; 1 sound tape reel: 7 in.
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV212; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV213; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV217; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR164; 1 sound cassette
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR167; 1 sound cassette
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated, afc2016057_dc050; 8 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated, afc2016057_dc476; Performed at American Museum of Natural History. Music by Geoffrey Gordon; 30 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Inanna Queen of Heaven and Earth, undated, afc2016057_dc034; Excerpt from performance at the American Museum of Natural History.; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Inanna and Glass Mountain with David Gonzalez, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV203; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - Isis and Osiris, February 21, 1985, AFC 2016/057: SR173; 1 sound cassette
    - Isis and Osiris, December 6, 1985, AFC 2016/057: SR174; 1 sound cassette
    - Isis and Osiris, December 13, 1985, AFC 2016/057: MV220; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Isis and Osiris, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV221; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Jacob and Esau, March 4, 1983, AFC 2016/057: SR175; 1 sound cassette
    - Japanese stories, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR176; 1 sound cassette
    - The Jazz Man, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR256; 1 sound tape reel: 5 in.
    - The Jazz Man, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR257; 1 sound tape reel: 5 in.
    - Joseph, December 15, 1985, AFC 2016/057: SR177; 1 sound cassette
    - Joseph, June 27, 1985, AFC 2016/057: SR178; 1 sound cassette
    - Joseph, 2003, afc2016057_dc092; 2001 recording studio remaster; 14 sound files (WAV)
    - Joseph, undated, afc2016057_dc093; 14 sound files (WAV)
    - Journey to the West, July 28, 2008, afc2016057_dc102; Accompanied by David Gonzalez on guitar. Performed in Central Park. Part 1.; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Journey to the West, October 15, 2008, afc2016057_dc125; Performed in Edmonds, Washington; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - Judith, April 4, 1996, AFC 2016/057: SR179; 1 sound cassette
    - Judith, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR180; 1 sound cassette
    - Judith, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR181; 1 sound cassette
    - Judith, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV334; 1 videocassette (BetacamSP)
    - Judith - Therese, Praise the Lord, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR182; 1 sound cassette
    - Kids Central Park, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV223; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Kokioko and Bear rehearsal, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR183; 1 sound cassette
    - Side A: Latin American Tales; Side B: The Boy and the Whale, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR184; 1 sound cassette
    - Layla and Majnun, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR185; 1 sound cassette
    - Layla and Majnun, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR186; 1 sound cassette
    - Layla and Majnun, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR187; 1 sound cassette
    - Layla and Majnun, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR188; 1 sound cassette
    - Layla and Majnun, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR189; 1 sound tape reel: 7 in.
    - Light in Israel, September 13, 1997
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR190; 1 sound cassette
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR191; 1 sound cassette
    - Little Ida's Flowers - rehearsal, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR192; 1 sound cassette
    - The Lute Player, June 5, 1999, AFC 2016/057: SR193; 1 sound cassette
    - Magic Orange Trees, October 9, 1994, AFC 2016/057: SR201; 1 sound tape reel: 10 in.
    - Magic Orange Trees, June 2008, afc2016057_dc054; Performed at the Glade, Central Park.; Tiger Gill; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Magic Orange Trees, November 8, 2009, afc2016057_dc048; Performed at New York University.; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Magic Orange Trees, February 18, 2010
      - Volume 1, afc2016057_dc098; 12 sound files (WAV)
      - Volume 2, afc2016057_dc098; 10 sound files (WAV)
    - Magic Orange Trees, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR194; 1 sound cassette
    - Magic Orange Trees, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR195; 1 sound cassette
    - Magic Orange Trees, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR196; 1 sound cassette
    - Magic Orange Trees, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR197; 1 sound cassette
    - Magic Orange Trees, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR198; 1 sound tape reel: 7 in.
    - Magic Orange Trees, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR199; 1 sound tape reel: 10 in.
    - Magic Orange Trees, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR200; 1 sound tape reel: 10 in.
    - The Magic Tree, September 14, 1994
      - DAT version, AFC 2016/057: SR202; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
      - DAT version, AFC 2016/057: SR203; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Maivor Haven, November 9, 2005, AFC 2016/057: MV224; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - The Man Who Became a Pirate, undated, afc2016057_dc306; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - May Time Storytelling Celebration, May 2, 1999, AFC 2016/057: SR205; 1 sound cassette
    - Maya Storm, February 5, 1979, AFC 2016/057: SR206; 1 sound cassette
    - Maya, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR207; 1 sound cassette
    - Michigan Storytelling Festival, October 2004, afc2016057_dc099; Diane Wolkstein, Michael Braudy, Mike Gilmore, and Mike Johnston perform Sunmother Wakes the World, The Glass Mountain, Bouki Dances the Kokioko, Goose with the Golden Feathers, and The Thief.; 6 sound files (WAV)
    - Monkey King, March 5, 1991
      - VHS version, AFC 2016/057: MV226; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc044; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, December 2, 2008, AFC 2016/057: MV225; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Monkey King, December 7, 2008, AFC 2016/057: MV227; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Monkey King, December 13, 2008
      - Part 2A, AFC 2016/057: MV233; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part 3A, AFC 2016/057: MV235; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Monkey King, March 2008, afc2016057_dc334; Rehearsals; 11 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, June 6, 2008
      - Rehearsal 1, AFC 2016/057: MV258; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Rehearsal 2, AFC 2016/057: MV259; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Monkey King Rehearsal and talk, June 28, 2008, AFC 2016/057: MV266; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Monkey King Diane and Volture Pick, October 27, 2008, AFC 2016/057: MV253; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Monkey King Diane with Mother's First Class, September 24, 2008, AFC 2016/057: MV254; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Monkey King, February 7, 2009
      - VHS version, AFC 2016/057: MV228; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc138; 5 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, September 28, 2009
      - Rehearsal 1 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV260; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Rehearsal 1 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV261; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Rehearsal 1 - DVD, afc2016057_dc137; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Rehearsal 2 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV262; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Rehearsal 2 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV263; 1 videocassette (VHS)